questions =  [
    {"id": 0, "effects": {"auth": 1, "right": -0.1},"question": "GLORY TO WERDZISTAN"},
    {"id": 1, "effects": {"auth": 1, "right": -1},  "question": "Werdz is best girl"},
    {"id": 2, "effects": {"auth": 1},               "question": "I rarely break server rules"},
    {"id": 3, "effects": {"auth": 0.5},             "question": "I can list every mod"},
    {"id": 4, "effects": {"right": -1},             "question": "I hornypost often"},
    {"id": 5, "effects": {"right": -1},             "question": "I hornypost other discord members"},
    {"id": 6, "effects": {"right": 1},              "question": "I hate hornyposters"},
    {"id": 7, "effects": {"right": -0.5},           "question": "Fourth is cute"},
    {"id": 8, "effects": {"right": -0.5},           "question": "Rushers is cute"},
    {"id": 9, "effects": {"right": -0.5},           "question": " is cute"},
    {"id": 10, "effects": {"auth": 1},              "question": "1984 is necesarry"},
    {"id": 11, "effects": {"auth": -0.5},           "question": "I inflict shame on other people"},
    {"id": 12, "effects": {"auth": 1},              "question": "I am a server mod (pls put Neutral if you're not)"},
];
